Jackie: (Exhales)
What the hell was that for?
Shall I call security,
or do you think
you can control yourself?
Stephanie: Are you proud
of yourself,
stealing from us?
Jackie: Was something stolen?
Stephanie: "Was something
stolen?"
Oh, don't you pretend with me.
How could you stoop so low?
Ridge: Well, don't feel bad.
What else could you have done?
Your mom just came in.
I'm on the phone with bridget.
Brooke: (Sighs)
Ridge: It's all true.
Jackie m. Stole our line.
Pam: (Sobbing)
Nick: Pam, are you okay?
Pam: (Gasps)
Oh! Oh, Nick. I'm sorry.
Oh, I-I didn't want you
to see me like this.
(Sighs)
Nick: Well, I-I can go
if you need to--
Pam: Oh, no, please don't.
(Sniffles)
I-I-I'm really not upset.
It--I--it's just--
in fact,
I'm really, really happy for you
and for Jackie m.
I just...
(Sighs)
Nick: It was
a heck of a show today.
Pam: (Sighs)
(Laughs) You betcha.
(Sniffles)
(Sighs)
Nick: So you
having some regrets?
Pam: Not really.
Certainly not about Stephanie.
She does not deserve my loyalty.
Nick: Mm-hmm.
Pam: But the others,
you know, I...
I feel a little bad.
It's kind of like
I'm making a choice
to leave my family today.
Nick: Only to join
a new family,
because you are part
of Jackie m. Now.
Pam: (Sighs)
(Whispers) Thanks.
Synced By YesCool
www.addic7ed.com
Eric: This is unbelievable.
Brooke: (Sighs)
Eric: How could Jackie
do this?
Brooke: How could Nick?
Ridge: We should have known
something was up
when they didn't accept
bill Spencer's deal.
Eric: Yeah.
Brooke: All of your
beautiful designs gone.
Hope: Hey.
I just heard. Is it true?
Brooke: I'm afraid so, honey.
Hope: The entire collection?
Ridge: Mother's there now
trying to sort things out.
Hope: Okay, how could they
get their hands on our designs?
We had so much security.
Brooke: We even hired
that new company.
Eric: No, no.
We screened that company.
Their reputation was five-star.
Brooke: So if somebody were
to come in from the outside--
Eric: No, I don't think so.
They--they would have
caught them.
They couldn't have sneaked by.
Hope: Uh, but they did.
Ridge: I don't think so.
Brooke: Oh.
I don't like
what you're suggesting.
Ridge: It's
the only explanation.
Eric: It was somebody
we know.
Somebody we trust
is stealing from us.
Brooke: And selling your
beautiful designs to Jackie m.
Eric: Thousands of hours
of work.
I was proud of this collection.
Hope: Who would do this?
Uh, it's so unfair.
Eric: (Sighs)
God, it makes me sick.
Brooke: Eric, we will find
who did this, okay?
Eric: (Sighs)
Oh, I'm sure we will, Brooke.
It's not gonna make me
feel any better, though.
Ridge: Or undo the damage.
Nick: With my mother?
You're sure?
No, no.
You were right to interrupt me.
Thanks for letting me know.
Pam: What--Jackie
is with Stephanie
in the building?
Nick: Backstage.
Pam: (Sighs)
Okay.
(Inhales sharply)
Okay, Nick.
Time for me to face the music.
Nick: Wait.
Now let's be smart about this.
Let's think this through.
There's no reason
that Stephanie would know
that it's you right now.
So... why not keep it that way?
Pam: (Sighs)
Stephanie: Is this revenge
because of Eric?
Jackie: (Scoffs)
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Stephanie: Well,
he--he led you to believe
there was a problem with our
relationship, and then he went
running to you for comfort.
Jackie: There was and he did,
but my heart
was far from broken.
Eric has bouts of courage
from time to time when he thinks
he's through with you.
Of course, people
don't believe him anymore.
I guess people
just like to be miserable.
Personally,
I wouldn't take revenge
on a man I pity.
Stephanie: So it's me?
You hate me this much?
Jackie: I think
you might be upset,
because I've shown something
today that was similar
to one of your designs,
maybe a few.
Stephanie: Similar?
SIM--SIM--similar?
Similar?!
You stole the whole line!
Jackie: Oh, Stephanie,
fashion goes in trends.
You know that.
If there were similarities,
it's because of that,
and who's to say
that we didn't have
the same creative buzz
at Jackie m. That you had?
Stephanie: Creative buzz?!
You haven't got a creative bone
in the whole damn building!
Oh, my God!
You've turned
into Sally spectra.
This place
has just become spectra,
what it used to be--
a knock-off place.
You've stolen everything.
You've become
the queen of knock-offs.
Is that what you really want?!
Well, I guess if the crown fits,
wear it.
Eric: Oh, my God.
Look what she did.
She makes one--
one little change,
and she thinks she can
pass it off as her own design.
Ridge: Click on the next one.
Brooke: Oh, no.
Eric: It's the showstopper.
Hope: (Sighs)
Ridge: They got everything,
every last design.
How the hell did they
get their hands on these?
(Camera shutter clicks)
Oliver: Uh, yeah, okay.
Um, well, yeah,
I-I heard it's everything,
but, uh, no one knows for sure.
I know, right?
Yeah, okay.
I-I'll tell him you called.
Sure.
Beverly: Hey, Oliver.
Oliver: Hi.
Beverly, right?
Beverly: Yeah.
I thought you worked down
in the photo studio.
Oliver: Yeah.
I-I'm filling in for Madison,
who's filling in for Pam.
Things are pretty crazy
around here
if you haven't noticed.
Beverly: What's going on?
Oliver: You haven't heard?
Beverly: No.
Oliver: Jackie m.
Just had a fashion show.
People are saying
they showed forrester designs.
Beverly: Why?
Who would want to buy
old designs?
Oliver: No, not old ones,
new ones,
the ones we were gonna use
in our show,
or versions of them, at least.
Beverly: Wow.
What--what--what does that mean?
Oliver: It means
they stole from us.
It means someone here
helped them.
Whoever did it
is gonna be in serious trouble.
Pam: Well, it's not gonna be
too hard for them to figure out,
sailor, especially when they see
that I'm working here.
I mean, that's still the plan,
right?
Nick: Of course.
But... is now the right time?
Pam: Yes.
I'm ready.
And I really need to be here,
Nick, especially now.
I can't be back at forrester
pretending that I didn't hurt
all those people.
Nick: No, no.
I-I understand completely.
It's--you know,
it's just a shame
we're gonna lose our connection
to all of those...
(Sighs)
Those beautiful designs...
Pam: Yeah.
Nick: Yeah, with you
in such a key position.
You know, Pam, you're the reason
that we had this fashion show.
Pam: You mean,
the longer I stay over there,
the longer Jackie m.
Would benefit?
Nick: Well,
they're gonna figure out
at some point,
but until then...
Pam: Keep... stealing?
Nick: Let's not
do anything rash, okay?
Pam: Okay.
Nick: As far as we know,
Stephanie's in the building,
and we don't know if she knows,
and maybe she does.
Either way,
if my mother plays this right,
which I think she will...
We could be helping each other
for... a long, long time.
Pam: (Sighs)
Stephanie: I understood
that you didn't want to take
the money from Spencer,
but was stealing
the only option?
Why didn't you come to me?
Jackie: No.
You do not get to pretend
that you were available,
that all I had to do
was reach out and you'd come
swooping in to help.
The moment that you thought
that Eric was interested in me,
you flipped that switch
in your head,
and I went from friend to foe...
Just like that.
You're hurting?
Well, so am I, Stephanie.
I came to your aid.
I swooped in to help you.
"Team Stephanie. Rah rah!"
You remember that?
They were fond memories.
Well, now they are gone.
They are over.
And all we are to each other
is competitors.
Stephanie: Who did you con
into stealing for you?
Jackie: Nobody.
Stephanie: Oh, please.
It's so apparent.
There was somebody
on the inside.
Did you throw a ton of money
at them,
or did you use your sex appeal?
Jackie: Not mine.
Stephanie: What?
Jackie: You have to leave,
okay?
I have just had
the showing of my career,
and I'm not
gonna have today ruined
by your ridiculous accusations.
Stephanie: The showing
of your career?
You stole from us!
You have stolen everything
from us.
You've cost us a fortune.
You...
(Sighs)
Okay, Jackie.
I'm gonna figure this out.
I am.
I'm gonna figure out
who the accomplice is,
and when I do,
it isn't going to be pretty
for either one of you.
And you know me.
(Door closes)
Pam: We should have heard
by now.
Nick: Well, not necessarily.
It's not like my mother can call
if Stephanie's in the middle
of a tirade.
Pam: I know,
but I'm--I'm worried about her.
When my sister
loses her temper--
(Gasps)
Jackie: Aha.
You heard she was here.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: Mother.
Pam: You're okay.
Jackie: Oh, yes, I'm fine.
I just stayed clear
of all the balconies
in the building.
Pam: Is she gone?
Jackie: Thankfully.
Pam: Whew.
Nick: Well, what happened?
Pam: Yeah, come on.
Don't keep us in suspense.
Does she know about me?
Jackie: (Scoffs)
Oh, Pam. You know Stephanie.
She doesn't ever
think about you.
Why should she start now?
Pam: (Scoffs)
Yeah, right.
Well, at least
she doesn't suspect me then?
Jackie: Not in the least.
Nick: There,
do you hear that?
Nothing has to change.
You continue to stay
at forrester, be our pipeline.
Pam: Oh,
I-I don't know, Nick.
I-I kind of thought that I'd be
free and clear of Stephanie
after today.
I mean, the thought
of going back there to forrester
and pretending--
Nick: No, no.
Just--just--just for
a while longer, okay,
just to see how many designs
you can actually get.
Jackie: Hmm.
Pam: Oh, I-I don't know.
Nick: Mother?
Jackie: Mm-hmm?
Nick: Do you think
we could have a moment?
Jackie: Yes, definitely.
I'll go and check,
see how everything's selling.
(Chuckles)
Pam: Okay.
Nick: Pam.
Pam: Yeah?
Nick: You have
individually saved Jackie m.
Words can't really express
my gratitude.
I would really appreciate
if you continued to help us.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: So I'm asking you
to do that
for me.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: Please.
Brooke: We should start
working on a letter to the press
and let everybody know that
the show has been cancelled.
Ridge: No, just postponed.
How the hell did we get
in this position?
(Door opens)
Eric: Stephanie.
Stephanie: She got
every single one of the designs.
Ridge: Yeah,
we saw the pictures.
Stephanie: When bridget
called me, I-I couldn't
believe--I couldn't believe
what I was hearing.
Eric: It's just unbelievable.
How could Jackie do this?
Stephanie: Well,
she's a thief.
I just talked to her.
She wouldn't admit it, and she
wouldn't tell me anything.
Eric: Yeah.
Ridge: Obviously,
she has an insider.
Stephanie: Yes, and I think
it behooves us to find them.
Ridge: You're damn right
we're gonna find them.
Hope: I think I might know.
Brooke: What?
Hope: She was
taking pictures, Stephanie.
I saw her.
Ridge: Of our designs?
Hope: You know she was.
Stephanie: Well, yes,
but just--it never--
Brooke: Who are you
talking about?
Stephanie: Beverly. Beverly.
Hope: The new intern.
I think she stole our designs.
Stephanie: (Sighs)
Pam: I want to keep at it
for you,
but I've been waiting so long,
Nick.
I have been fantasizing
about this day
when I would
finally tell Stephanie off.
Nick: N-no, you can't.
She doesn't know it was you.
You can't give yourself away
when there's so much more
that you can do, Pam.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: You've got
to make peace with Stephanie.
Pam: No! No.
Not after the way
she treated me.
Nick: If you
confront her now,
it's over.
Don't give in
to that temptation.
See how far
that you can take this.
She doesn't know it was you,
and maybe she never will.
Think about what you can do
for Jackie m.
Pam: So I-I just...
Go back there?
Nick: Just as if
nothing's changed.
Pam: Put a big smile
on my face for Stephanie
and answer the phones,
pour coffee, bake for them?
No, Nick.
This is where I belong now,
not there.
Nick: And you will be here.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: And we'll be meeting
all the time.
Pam: I can't do it.
I can't.
It--it's one thing if I'm here,
but being back over there
and looking in their faces,
the people I betrayed--
Eric, ridge,
my nieces and nephews.
I-I can't.
I-I...
I can't.
Nick: You can.
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: Can't you?
Nick: Now I want you
to go back to forrester,
make nice with Stephanie...
Pam: (Inhales sharply)
Nick: And act like
you have nothing to do...
Pam: (Sighs)
Nick: With stealing
those designs.
Pam: When you kiss me
like that,
I feel like
there's nothing I can't do.
Okay.
I'll go back.
I'll take the designs.
Heck, I'll take office supplies
if you need them.
Nick: No, no. No, no.
Pam: No?
(Laughs)
Nick: The designs are--
the designs are fine.
Pam: Okay.
Nick: You might want
to get back over there.
You'll--with all the mayhem,
they'll notice
if somebody's missing
and get suspicious.
Pam: One more little kiss,
you know, for courage?
Nick: For courage.
Pam: Yeah.
Mwah!
Okeydokey, sailor man.
Nick: (Laughs)
Ah.
Pam: I am on a mission now.
Nick: Oh.
Pam: I will be that Pammy
that everybody knows and loves.
Nobody will suspect a thing.
Oh, hello, Jackie.
Jackie: (Gasps) Oh!
Pam: Toodles. Can't talk now.
I got a company to keep afloat.
Nick: (Laughs)
Jackie: She's heading
back to forrester?
Nick: Yes, she is.
She decided to, uh, continue
helping us and bring designs
as long as she can.
Jackie: So how did you
convince her?
What did you say?
Or was it something
you did?
Nick: (Smacks lips)
Jackie: Mm-hmm.
Nick: (Pops lips)
Eric: When she gets back,
send her up here right away.
Ridge: Suspicious,
to say the least.
Hope: Yeah, I mean,
who does that?
Who takes pictures
of the designs?
Brooke: But if she
didn't know not to...
Eric: Look,
how--how did she react when--
when you called her on it?
Did she seem like she was lying?
Stephanie: No.
No, not at all.
As a matter of fact,
she apologized immediately.
She was very genuine
and straightforward.
Honestly, I never thought
to question.
(Laughs)
(Knock on door)
Stephanie: She's here.
Eric: All right.
Let's not, uh,
jump all over her, all right?
Be careful.
Hope: I think
it's pretty obvious.
Eric: (Sighs)
(Knock on door)
Beverly: Hello?
Ridge: Come in.
Beverly: Hi.
I-I was told you
were looking for me.
Brooke: We have
some questions.
Ridge: Close the door.
Beverly: Something's wrong.
Is this about
the Jackie m. Fashion show?
Stephanie: I have something
I'd like to ask you.
And, Beverly, I want you
to tell me the truth.
Beverly: Okay.
Stephanie: Did you
take our designs
and sell them to Jackie marone?
Beverly: What?!
Stephanie: Did you?
Beverly: Mrs. forrester.
Stephanie: Just answer
the question--yes or no.
Hope: I saw you, Beverly,
taking pictures
of the entire collection.
Beverly: Yeah,
a-and I explained.
Hope: I know--I know you did,
that you--you didn't know
any better.
But that's not good enough
right now, okay?
Because all
of their really hard work
has just ended up
on the Jackie m. Runway.
Somebody stole from us.
Somebody handed over
every single one of our designs
to the marones.
Was it you?
Did you steal
our entire collection?
Synced By YesCool
www.addic7ed.com