Previously on "The Bold Type"...
You're ready to introduce me
as your girlfriend,
but you're not ready to go down on me?
I guess I was a little, uh,
worried and scared.
Everyone knows that Sutton
has been sleeping with him.
It's the only reason she's getting
- all these styling credits.
- It's a gamble.
All of it. But I'm putting my money down
on my career and believing
that love will fall in place.
My first subject is Emma Cox.
I love that a customer knows
a homeless woman
is gonna benefit from her purchase.
Three of our clients
wound up in the hospital
- with infections.
- Jane.
So in about one minute, your vertical's
going to go live. Just a heads-up,
- I made a few adjustments.
- Oh, shit.
- Enjoy your Squeeze Press!
- Thank you.
_
- Hey.
- Where are you?
Squeeze Press.
At a table facing the office.
Wait, what? I thought
we said the Midtown location?
I've been looking forward
to this all morning!
Why would we go to Midtown?
Because that's where my appointment was.
Hold on, it's Jane.
Are you at the Midtown location?
I'm at the Brooklyn location,
like we discussed.
- Brooklyn?
- I'm in Midtown.
Yeah, and I'm in Madison Square Park.
- I'm dying to know.
- Okay, just tell us.
- How was it?
- Well...
then you know where to find me.
Oh, and ladies?
- It's worth it.
- Kat!
First one there gets the details.
No!
- Yes, yes, yes!
- No! No!
No!
Oh, my God, I can't believe you guys.
- And, Jane, your shoes.
- Oh, please, she doesn't care.
Yeah, the only thing
I care about right now
is you telling us what it was like
to go down on Adena.
Go ahead.
Well, uh, it was awesome.
I mean, I was completely
freaked out at first.
- Of course.
- Who wouldn't be?
Then I realized
I have one of these,
and I know what I like.
So, I did it.
And I liked it. A lot.
- Ooh!
- That's amazing.
And things with Adena are awesome.
- God, I miss Richard sex.
- Oh, babe.
You just need a distraction.
I just want to like a guy again,
you know?
Yeah.
Oh, great.
- I have to go deal with this Emma Cox takedown.
- _
Actually, we have to go too.
- Jacqueline pitch meeting.
- All right.
Uh, hey. Baby?
The Emma Cox thing is gonna be fine.
- Mm...
- Mm-kay.
Guys, are you gonna
walk with me like this?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Off to work.
Hey, Victoria. Do you have a second?
What's up?
My piece on Emma Cox
is completely different
than what I handed in.
Do you know why
we call this place "Incite"?
- Because it...
- Because we incite conversations.
Your nuanced piece on when
good intentions go bad
didn't do that.
But the part where Emma Cox
brands OTR as charitable,
even after her product
makes homeless women sick
was interesting.
So I made that the article.
I get that. Um...
It's just, you hired me for my voice...
When it aligns with "Incite's" brand.
You just missed the mark this time.
I just wish that I would have seen it
before it went live.
At... at "Scarlet"...
This is not "Scarlet," Jane.
Right.
Another hero caught
beating off on camera.
How hard is it to keep
your junk in your trunk?
I don't think you're using that right.
- Not the point.
- When in doubt,
- don't pull it out.
- Exactly.
Not that hard.
Ooh, I do not envy any of you
having to navigate
dating in this climate.
So there is something else
that we need to talk about.
Our allies.
The guys who show up at women's rallies,
and who speak up when others are silent.
I want to do a roundup of honorable men.
Good doctors, firefighters,
human rights activists.
Alex, you'll do the interviews.
And we'll make it a fashion spread.
Can't we just do a write-up?
You know how I hate styling
the general population.
I have faith in you, Oliver.
And you have a great support staff.
And a meditation app, if you need it.
Kat, we need to bank some content
for Snapchat, and this photo shoot
will be a perfect place to start.
Hashtag "they're not all bad,"
you know... you make that better.
- Yeah.
- All right, so,
what's in the hopper for our
"Love and Lust" section?
Uh, household appliances
that will charge up
- your sex life.
- Electric toothbrush.
What?
What, nobody else...
And a Waterpik.
- People still use those?
- They will,
- after they read my article.
- Hmm.
- Give me your top six.
- Sure.
All right, everyone, that's it.
Uh, Kat, can you hang back for a moment?
Sure.
Now that you are a department head,
I'm going to need your bio
for speaking engagements
and media tie-ins.
I really want you out there
as the face of social.
- Great.
- You do have a bio, right?
I have...
a Twitter bio and an Insta bio.
All right, well,
I'm gonna need something
a little bit more professional.
You know,
just a couple paragraphs,
make it interesting.
People are gonna want to
know who Kat Edison is.
Okay.
Richard. Good to see you.
To what do I owe this honor?
A board seat just became available.
Oh. Did someone die, or move to Boca?
Stanley Rogers retired
to spend more time with his family.
And you're telling me this because...
I think you should go for it.
It'd be a lot of fun
to have you upstairs.
We could really
shake things up from the inside.
Mm, that would be fun,
and I love the idea
of another woman being upstairs.
But you and I both know
I'm not leaving "Scarlet."
Unless, of course,
that's no longer a conflict.
No, it is.
I figured it was a long shot,
but you can't blame a guy
for trying, right?
Well, keep me updated on who they find.
Of course.
Everything else good?
Yeah, good enough.
Red. Men like you.
Walk with me.
- Figures.
- You don't know this,
well, because you're young,
but styling the general population
is hell, even if they are handsome.
Which is why I want you
to be my right hand.
- Got it.
- And my left.
Here's your binder of extraordinary men.
Pick five who can be
here in the morning.
- Tomorrow morning?
- You'll need to fit them.
These are not models,
so they are not one size fits all.
Oh, and Red, these guys are amateurs
when it comes to photo shoots,
so they're going to need
a lot of hand-holding.
You're welcome.
_
"Emma Cox is a fraud."
Oh, my God, this is crazy.
Are "Incite" readers always this harsh?
Yep.
And I take it you don't agree with them.
Yeah, because they only
have one side of the story.
I mean, she did one bad thing,
and it wasn't on purpose.
Oof! Brutal.
Come on, we have a pitch meeting.
Yeah, I'll be there in a second.
_
Hi, this is Emma Cox.
Please leave a message.
Hi, Emma. This is Jane Sloan
from "Incite." I just wanted to say
how sorry I am.
Ooh, working on your bio?
Kind of.
Is that Susan and Marcus?
Yeah.
Huh.
I want you to meet them.
I'm supposed to have dinner
with them tomorrow night,
so maybe we could
invite them over, or...
Um...
are you sure you want me to be there?
I know you've never introduced
anyone you were dating
to your parents before.
Yes, I'm sure.
Not to mention, a woman.
They know. They're cool.
They want to meet the
person I'm crazy about.
Okay.
Then, uh, I'd better do my research.
Mm-hmm.
Each page just keeps
getting better and better.
Their careers are very impressive.
Who are you? "Their careers
are very impressive?"
Have you even looked
- at this binder?
- It's a binder of professional men.
It is a binder of hot men,
and you get to fit them.
Because men like me.
Okay, someone's cocky.
Oliver's words, not mine.
Do you think Oliver wants my help
because he heard people talking,
and he thinks I'm the office flirt?
No.
I think he wants your help
because you're good at your job.
- All right.
- But that doesn't mean
you can't still enjoy some eye candy
with your best friend.
How cute is this guy?
And he's a doctor.
With a free clinic.
I think I have an itch.
You do know this is a
round-up of good guys
in light of all the
sexual harassment claims?
Oh, and I'm objectifying them.
Yeah.
I see the irony, and I'm okay with it.
Why did I leave "Scarlet," again?
Because you wanted to do
hard-hitting journalism.
Well, you know what I would hit hard?
That.
Oh, what is this?
What's "Sorry Not Sorry Jane Sloan"?
It's getting retweeted like crazy.
Hi, Emma. This is Jane Sloan
from "Incite." I just wanted to say
how sorry I am.
That's not the article I wrote.
It was turned into a total hit piece.
- Call Kat.
- Yeah.
If you could give me a
call when you get this,
that would be great.
Great. 956 retweets.
How could she do this?
She put my voicemail on Twitter.
Why would she humiliate me like this?
I was trying to apologize.
Maybe I should just email
her my original article,
- and she'll take it down.
- No.
Have you learned nothing
from this experience?
Well, I should at least email Victoria
- and tell her what happened...
- Hey!
- Do not touch...
- No, no.
...the computer.
- But Victoria is...
- Will handle it.
Remember when the stripper sued you?
Jacqueline took care of it.
This is way above your pay grade.
Wonderful.
"Sorry Not Sorry" is trending.
Not the Demi Lovato version.
Yeah, but it's totally gonna blow over.
- Right, Kat?
- Absolutely.
These things have a 24-hour lifespan.
Just wanted to say how sorry...
so-so-sorry I am.
How sorry I am.
This is Jane-Jane-Jane
Jane-Jane-Jane Sloan.
I just wanted to say
how sorry... so-so-sorry I am.
How sorry I am.
This is Jane-Jane-Jane
Jane-Jane-Jane Sloan.
I just wanted to say how sorry...
- so-so-sorry I am.
- Sorry.
How sorry I am.
It's not funny.
Hi, can I help you?
Tim Benson. NYFD lieutenant.
Sage, "Scarlet" sex writer.
I'm here for a fitting.
- We all are.
- Okay.
Oh, right!
Right, uh,
sit tight, I will be right back.
Okay.
Oh! Whoops! Excuse me.
Sutton, there's some men in reception.
Real men. Not models.
People with impressive jobs.
Uh, yeah. Right. Whatever.
Uh, do you want me to wait
with the guys in reception?
- I really don't mind.
- That's okay.
Just send them over to me.
Okay, if you need anything,
- I am...
- Just send 'em on down.
Okay.
Hey. Can I ask you a favor?
- What's up?
- Okay, I was just wondering
if you could take a look at my bio
and make sure it's reading okay
before I give it to Jacqueline.
I'd be honored.
Hmm. Hmm.
Oh, my God, I...
I already hate this.
I could never be a writer.
Well, see, the key is to add
- as much detail as possible.
- Okay.
Like, you could add the fact
that you're black.
It'll read something like, "Kat Edison
is 'Scarlet' magazine's
first black female department head."
See, that sounds impressive.
Yeah, but it's also irrelevant.
You know, I'm a department head.
That has nothing to do
with the color of my skin.
Okay...
it's a big part of who you are.
Yeah, but I'm also part white,
and no one asked me to write that down.
Not the same thing, but okay.
Uh, any other suggestions?
Yeah... Kat, you have
this really cool opportunity
to be a role model
for young black girls.
Don't you want that?
Why would you ask me that?
Of course I want that.
But I want it regardless of my race,
not because of it.
It's what's on the inside that matters.
But you're black on the inside too, Kat.
Oh, really?
Are... are you questioning
my blackness right now?
Because, uh, up until very recently,
you were wearing khakis and cardigans,
which is just about the whitest
fashion statement imaginable.
That is an interesting projection
- of internalized racism.
- Oh, cool.
- So now I'm a racist?
- I didn't say that.
Yeah, you didn't have to.
This'll only take a second.
Oh, no problem.
When in "Scarlet," am I right?
If you're Sutton, then yes.
Why do you get all
the good assignments, Sutton?
It's 'cause men like her.
At least that's why
Oliver gave her the job.
We're... We're just jealous.
Speak for yourself.
Don't listen to them.
Oh!
Okay, you're good! You can...
put your clothes back on now.
Thank you.
Remember: measure twice, cut once.
I just wanted to say how sorry...
so-so-sorry I am.
How sorry I am.
This is Jane-Jane-Jane
Jane-Jane-Jane Sloan.
I just wanted to say how sorry...
so-so-sorry I am.
How sorry I am...
Victoria, I'm...
- I'm so sorry.
- Apparently.
Those words just seem
to flow out of your mouth.
I know I screwed up.
I should have never
contacted Emma, but...
You did screw up. We just need
to change the narrative
and show that "Incite"
is a serious publication.
I've already booked
an interview on NY14.
Oh, thank you so much
for taking care of this.
Me?
No. You're going on television,
and it's live.
Have we media trained you yet?
No.
Okay, you ready?
I was born ready.
Just another one of the
things I love about you.
Oh!
Coming!
- Hey.
- So good to see you.
Oh...
Hey, babe. Come here.
Hey, missy.
Mom, Dad,
this is Adena.
It's so good to meet you, Adena.
Such a pleasure.
And, uh...
so nice to meet you, Dr. Edison...
- Ah, hey. Marcus.
- Marcus.
Come on, come on.
Wardrobe came in for tomorrow,
and unless one of your honorable men
is a pirate...
I must have written the
measurements down wrong.
I thought you grew up
making your own clothes.
Or was that just a story
you sold me to get you hired?
No, I made my entire wardrobe.
Good. Then you can fix this.
And whatever's going on,
for the love of God,
get it together.
- Hi.
After you.
Uh, I just realized I forgot something.
I mean, I went to him
for a simple suggestion,
and then he told me that
I should add the fact
that I'm the first black
female department head.
I just don't really see
how that kind of detail is necessary.
Your bios don't list your race.
Because it has nothing
to do with our ability
- to treat patients.
- Exactly!
The color of my skin has no bearing
on my performance as a department head.
No one said it did.
Well, Alex seems to think
it's my responsibility
- or something...
- No, your responsibility
- is to be true to yourself
- Yeah.
You don't need labels to do that.
But... why are labels a bad thing?
My bio literally reads,
"proud Muslim lesbian."
It's a part of who I am.
Why wouldn't I want everyone to know?
Oh.
Excuse me.
You know what, this is Jacqueline,
so I'm just gonna take it real quick.
I'll be right back.
Hi, Jacqueline!
It's important you hit
all the talking points.
Other than admitting you
were wrong to call Emma,
and apologize,
this is not about Jane Sloan.
It's about preserving
the integrity of "Incite."
- It's about?
- Uh, "Incite" being
a hard-hitting,
factually accurate news outlet.
Exactly.
Emma Cox misrepresented
her organization.
How did she misrepresent
her organization?
Uh, by calling the company "charitable,"
even after her product
made a group of homeless women sick.
Remember, "Incite"
chases the stories that matter,
- even when it's difficult.
- And, um...
what if they ask me about
why I reached out to apologize to Emma?
Tell the truth.
You're new to "Incite"
and hard-hitting journalism.
And you got too personally invested.
And, Jane, your style.
You're gonna have to lose all of that
for the interview.
You're representing "Incite" now.
Not "Scarlet."
Of course.
So...
- she's great, right?
- She is.
- Dad?
- What are her parents like?
Uh...
honestly, I don't really know.
I mean, she talks to her mom a lot,
but I don't know much about her dad.
I think she left home kind of early.
- That's interesting.
- Oh, please,
do not psychoanalyze my girlfriend.
- Marcus.
- No, what?
I mean she's rebellious,
the way she insists
on people knowing who she
is and what she stands for.
- Mm-hmm.
- It just seems almost...
- adolescent.
- Okay, how about this?
How about, "Thanks for dinner, Kat."
And, "I'm glad to see you happy."
Thanks for dinner, Kat.
Good night.
- I'm so happy you're home.
- Yeah.
- Love you, baby.
- Bye.
I always thought side-by-side
washer and dryers
were a waste of space until now.
Did you know that women
can have six different kinds...
It's not important.
- Okay.
- So let me guess.
Another old white guy.
You wanted a woman, right?
- We got Cleo Williams.
- The digital fitness mogul?
Yeah. Her perspective is impressive,
and since we're revamping
our online image,
made sense to bring her on.
Send me her contact info.
I want to welcome her properly.
Your parents seem lovely.
Yeah.
You know, they try.
Even though they are psychiatrists.
Well, they didn't mess you up.
Yeah, I hope not.
You know, what I said earlier, um,
about your bio. It's up to you.
- Yeah, I know.
- We all have our own way.
And mine has always been
to put it all out there.
I... I can't imagine
living any differently.
But...
that's just how I do things.
Doesn't make my way
or Alex's way any better
or worse than yours.
Uh, Jacqueline? This is Cleo.
Oh, Cleo!
I'm so happy you could stop by.
Oh, are you kidding?
I am thrilled to finally meet you.
I've been a fan of yours
since I was in my 20s.
Well, now you're here
on the board, overseeing "Scarlet."
- Mm.
- Uh, please.
- Thank you.
- Coffee?
Oh, no, that stuff will kill you.
Well, I am hearing many
wonderful things about you
- from the board.
- Oh.
- They are very excited.
- Well, I am hugely excited
for the opportunity. Particularly,
the chance to expand digital.
What made you want to get
into the digital space
- to begin with?
- Besides the fact
that it's the future of everything?
You do know that our print magazine
sets the trends,
and digital comments on them.
Yes, of course. But, in my experience,
I've seen the power of the internet.
When I first started,
I was just a bored mom,
making these workout videos
to share with my other mom friends.
Now I run a fitness empire
that reaches millions
from the palm of my hand.
And it allows me to
have dinner on the table
every night for my family.
I can have my homemade rice cakes
and eat them too, I guess.
All while doing squats.
And taking selfies.
Should we take one for
my Instagram followers?
I think they'd be really
thrilled to see an image of me
with Jacqueline Carlyle.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Sutton, a bit of help?
Uh...
Hands-on, Red.
- Uh, let me help you.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Cool, thanks.
You're only eating the green ones.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing, I'm fine.
Mm.
- How about a Boomerang?
- Okay.
It's social media, be positive.
Red!
- We going with that one?
- That's fine.
Mm-hmm.
We have a problem.
Apparently he can deliver a baby
without breaking a sweat,
but ask him to smile
for the camera, and he freezes
like a deer in headlights.
Go over there and get...
get him to relax,
for the love of God.
I need good photographs.
I'm a glorified fluffer.
- How's it going, Kat?
- I am getting great snaps.
Good, good. How's your bio coming?
Bio. Uh, yeah.
- It's almost done.
- Yeah? Good.
I need it on my desk tomorrow morning.
You got it.
Still sitting on that bio, huh?
I really don't feel like talking.
I didn't mean for things
to get so heated.
Nope, it's all good.
I just thought that you...
you've always been this
super confident badass.
You speak your mind.
You stand up for what you want.
Point is, you never back down.
Not with your friends,
not your girlfriend,
and definitely not with work.
But when I brought up
adding "black" to your bio,
a wall goes up?
Yeah, you're right.
Do you know how everyone
always wants to...
be able to put you in a box, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Black, white,
girl, boy.
Even those standardized tests
they make you take as a kid.
You know,
where you have to fill in the bubbles?
I remember getting to the section
that says, "Select your race,
Caucasian or African-American,"
you don't have any other choice...
and thinking...
like, how do I pick?
I mean, 'cause if...
if I pick, uh...
if I pick black,
then I'm rejecting my mom.
And if I pick white,
then I'm rejecting my dad.
So what did you pick?
Well, actually, I just left it blank.
It was easier to deny
both than to pick one.
But...
you're not a kid anymore.
And standing up for who you are matters.
Yeah, I know.
Chad Horford. Nice to meet you.
Jane Sloan.
You're nervous. Don't be nervous.
It's the first time I've done
something like this.
Ah, don't worry about it. It'll be good.
We're on air in two seconds.
Hello, New York.
If you're a fan of "Incite,"
then you've probably
heard of Jane Sloan,
best known for her apology
to OTR's Emma Cox
that went viral. Now, Jane is here
to set the record straight
in her own words.
- Thank you for having me.
- We have a full slate,
so let's get right to it.
You wrote an article
on Emma Cox, which,
according to your now
very public apology,
was heavily edited.
So what happened?
Is "Incite" fabricating their stories?
No.
"Incite" is a hard-hitting,
factually accurate news outlet.
She misrepresented her company
as a charitable organization,
and "Incite" readers
deserve to hear that story
as much as anything else.
Even though it caused her
to lose funding for her company?
I allowed myself to get
too personally invested
in Emma Cox.
Hmm. I'm sure there are a lot
of aspiring journalists
watching right now
who appreciate your candor.
Well, there you have it.
Setting the record straight,
that's Jane Sloan. We'll be right back
- to meet New York's...
- I'm sorry,
if I could just say...
Um...
I do think that Emma Cox
is making great strides for women.
She is revolutionizing feminine hygiene.
Her cups are eco-friendly
and affordable.
Okay, are... are you saying...
I'm saying that she made one mistake:
not recognizing the sanitary conditions
needed for her product.
But people make mistakes.
And if they're good people,
they course-correct.
Which Emma did,
when she made new disposable cups
for less optimal conditions.
So, "Incite" was factually inaccurate.
I think that we're all so quick
to take each other down,
to find someone to blame.
"Incite" is not all right or all wrong,
just like Emma Cox is not
all good or all bad.
And when we sensationalize people
for the purpose of getting more eyes
on a story, that story gets lost.
Okay, then.
Something for all of us to think about.
- Thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
We'll be right back.
And, we're clear.
That was great.
This guy needs to relax.
What do you think?
How's it going?
I don't feel like myself at all.
I know exactly what you mean.
You're on display. You're being judged.
I don't know about that.
It's not a good feeling.
Red!
What the hell is going on?
Okay, you can't take
simple measurements,
you can't fix a guy's tie,
and that guy looks
more uncomfortable now
than when I asked you to talk to him.
Oliver. Let me handle this.
- What's wrong?
- Um...
some of the assistants found out
about me and Alex.
And you went through the
proper HR channel, so...
No, I know. We're not together.
Not since you caught
us in the stairwell.
Oh.
Okay, um...
so what's the problem?
When the assistants found out,
they started to talk
about Alex giving me
preferential treatment.
That's not why I was
getting the assignments.
- I know that.
- No, of course not.
But then Oliver assigned
me this photo shoot.
He could have picked anybody,
and he chose me because he thinks
that I work well with men.
I felt people in the office
judging me for that.
And I started to second-guess
how I carry myself, and how I...
- use my sexuality...
- Sutton.
You are a people person.
And men are people.
It's that simple.
It's just with everything
that's been going on lately...
Yes, it is undoubtedly...
a very complicated time
for men and women
in the workplace.
I mean, as stories continue to come out,
we're all checking ourselves,
but we cannot lose sight
of who we truly are.
And we cannot dim our light
that makes us special.
You have a magnetic personality, Sutton.
That is a good thing.
Don't let anybody tell you otherwise.
Okay.
Now, you get back out there,
and make that person...
...photogenic, please.
I'm on it.
Okay, Ben. You want to finish this up,
I'm here to help you make that happen.
- Let's talk, just me and you.
- Okay.
Okay.
Question number one:
why are you doing this?
It's good press for the clinic.
Mm-hmm. So is taking out an ad.
What are you not telling me?
Did you lose a bet?
- I don't gamble.
- Really?
But if you must know,
I have a list of things
- that make me uncomfortable.
- A list.
So what, like a reverse bucket list?
Mm-hmm. Being photographed
- is one of them.
- Okay.
- So you enjoy being uncomfortable.
- No, I hate it.
But it reminds me that I'm alive, so...
Alive and uncomfortable?
That sounds terrible.
- It does, doesn't it?
- Yes!
That is so weird.
I'm just kidding.
That's it. All right.
Got it. Next.
- Thanks for meeting me.
- Of course.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Yep.
What is it?
Why are we...
so against labeling ourselves?
Uh, well, I guess it's because
your mother and I, we feel that, um,
it's what's on the inside that matters.
Right, but...
I kind of think it's more than that.
The other night, you asked me...
about Adena's parents.
So what about your parents, Dad?
I mean I know everything
about grandma and grandpa.
But...
I don't know anything
about Dad's side of the family.
So why is that?
My childhood was a lot different
from yours, Kat.
I grew up with blacks
on one side of the city
and whites on the other.
And the label of race?
We didn't want that for you.
And I don't think we did such a bad job.
You're confident. You're successful.
Everything you guys are saying...
kind of just feels like a way to avoid
really talking about it, and I'm trying
to understand why.
Maybe it's my fault.
When you were little,
and I would take you to the park,
people assumed you
weren't biologically mine.
Maybe I avoided labels because
I just wanted to be your mom.
I didn't want to be your white mom.
Sweetheart...
if we ever made you feel
that you cannot take
ownership of who you are...
that was not our intention.
You're a grown woman.
You're beautiful,
smart, strong...
These are your choices to make.
Not ours.
Nice work today, Red.
Good to have you back.
Hey, Jane. How'd it go?
Well, I went off script,
so I'm not entirely sure.
But I feel good about it,
so that's something.
- How was the shoot?
- You know what?
I love men. And men love me.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
Well, that's cause for celebration.
- Should we get drinks?
- You read my mind.
There's just one thing
I have to do first.
Kay.
Hey, Mitzi.
So this slut-shaming thing you're doing.
- It's got to stop.
- I wasn't...
You were.
I know it, and, unfortunately,
a few of the assistants also know it.
But we don't tear each other down.
Not as women.
And definitely not
as women of "Scarlet."
If you want some competition,
I'm totally up for that,
but it has to be based
on merit and talent,
and not petty gossip.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Cool. Hey, guys!
- Who wants to get a drink?
- Let's do it.
- Yeah.
- Is that on your list?
Cheers!
Okay, how great
did everybody feel today?
- Awesome.
- You looked great.
You looked great, you looked great,
- and you looked great.
- Well, thank you.
Come here.
There's somebody that
I want you to meet.
- Hi.
- Hi, Jane.
This is Ben. Ben, this is Jane.
Oh, my God!
You guys are both great people,
who like to make really
weird to-do lists.
Thank you for the awkward introduction.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Uh, so...
- Drinks.
- Yeah.
Hello.
Do you want to talk?
Yeah, but not right now.
Right now, I want to drink.
I can make that happen. Bartender!
- Tequila or tequila?
- Tequila.
Thank you.
♪ Here we go ♪
♪ We have to raise the roof ♪
♪ Raise it up till it's right ♪
♪ Not goin' nowhere ♪
Oh, I love this song.
- I have to go dance.
- Okay.
♪ All my people ♪
♪ Pimps and divas ♪
♪ Come on and walk this way ♪
Oh, hey!
- ♪ All my people ♪
♪ Pimps and divas ♪
♪ It's time we all
went for a drink ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
Hey.
Hey, morning.
You going to work already?
Yeah, I, uh...
promised Jacqueline I'd have
my bio in first thing, so...
These things can be hard to look at.
Yeah...
and especially when you've been raised
with rose-colored glasses.
Your parents...
they did what they believed
was best for you at the time.
Yeah, I know.
But I also know that I chose
to keep those glasses on.
Long after I moved out.
Kat, it's...
it's okay.
Come here.
_
Hey. Thanks.
So what did you choose?
I am "Scarlet" magazine's
first black female department head.
Sounds impressive.
And I'm so proud to be biracial.
But...
for right now, it feels important
to embrace this part of myself.
Hold that!
Thanks. Oh, good morning, Richard.
Jacqueline.
- You get a chance to meet Cleo?
- I did.
And...
She won't be joining our poker night,
if that's what you're asking.
But I think she'll be
an asset to the board.
And a fresh perspective.
Still wish you were
riding to the top with me.
Maybe one day, Richard. Not yet.
Hi, Jacqueline, it's Cleo.
I just saw the layout
for next month's issue.
It's gorgeous. Had a few thoughts.
Call me, let's discuss.
- Victoria?
- Just the person
I wanted to see. Have a seat.
We all make mistakes.
The important thing is
that we learn from them.
Yes, uh,
that's exactly what I was going for
with my angle on Emma Cox.
I made a mistake recently...
when I thought you would
be a good fit for "Incite."
But I...
It was... it was a good interview, I...
I did what you said.
I hit all my talking points.
Jane, you went on television
to represent "Incite."
- You made it about yourself.
- No, I...
I was trying to make a point...
Jane. Stop.
You're fired.
- synced and corrected by sot26 -
www.addic7ed.com